<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="histoire1">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Saint Sorlin</item>
            <item name="genre">Kids</item>
            <item name="titre">A sacred Christmas</item>
            <item name="resume">Tales for children on Christmas.</item>
            <item name="histoire">
Simon tirelessly roamed the beach in search of driftwood for his sculptures. But the equinox tides were stingy, only twigs remained here and there on the shore. The setting sun was shining a ray brighter than the others at a distant point reflecting a glitter of crystal. It was almost three long years ago that Solange, his wife, was taken away by the disease. Simon looked pensive and then walked back to that barely lit spot.\n
- Christmas soon, he hissed, as if I had that to do! All those idiots flocking to the stores spend the hard-earned money. Make gifts to hypocrites who do not deserve it. What a bunch of morons.\n
So was Simon\'s existence. Solitary, sculptor on wood at his hours, nothing reconciled him with life. Arrived on the bright spot he discovered half-emerged, a bottle of glass. He unearthed it and noticed a sheet of thin paper folded inside. It was stronger than him, he smashed the bottle against a big flat pebble. Among the pieces of glass, the sheet of paper appeared. Simon seized her and incredulously deciphered a writing made of simple words.\n
The message was childish:\n
"Come and get me, I live in Sainte Cecile, my name is Teo. "\n
- You do not miss a toupee! I do not know you, if you do not even exist! Exclaims Simon.\n
On the way back, his emotions betrayed him. Maybe this kid really needed someone. Like himself, most certainly, he was aware of it. His grumpy hermit life was in a bind. Arrived at the red ocher facade of his little seaside house, envy took him to mourn his lost happiness forever.\n
- And you Solange, what would you do in my place?\n
He reassured himself and rolled his eyes, the two fists stretched out towards the horizon Simon let out his anger.\n
- Go to the devil!\n
The next day he went to the garage where his old Renault 5 was sleeping, turned the key. The engine purred happily. He took the road to the Sainte Cécile orphanage located just twenty minutes.\n
In the villages crossed, the Christmas decorations rivaled with a colorful gaiety and the shop windows of the enchanted scenes. Sleds, reindeer, goblins, snowy decorations and Christmas fathers of course animated the streets. The carefree passers-by seemed to evolve into another dimension. Something magical was preparing, then?\n
The courtyard of the Sainte Cécile orphanage was sober, gray and breathed tranquility. The large imposing building, pierced with dozens of windows, sent the light back to the visitor of the day.\n
Simon wondered if he had done well on Christmas Eve in this unattractive mansion. At the reception, a nun with a cheerful face greeted him like the incarnate Messiah.\n
- I am Sister Caroline, we are waiting for you impatiently. Children are excited like fleas. It\'s impossible to hold them until tonight and it\'s barely four o\'clock! Make yourself aware.\n
- I\'m not the one you expect. Replied Simon, taken aback.\n
- But brother Jean is bedridden, he can not do Santa Claus for children like every year. Nobody contacted you?\n
The happy face gave way to a pouting pout.\n
- No, or rather not directly. That is, I found a message in a bottle on the beach. This is a certain Teo, do you know him? I know you find this situation grotesque. Excuse me for the inconvenience, goodbye my sister. I will send you a check to support your work.\n
Simon turned on his heel when a flock of kids jostled him happily, failing to knock him back.\n
- We want to see Santa Claus, Santa Claus, Santa Claus ...\n
- Julie, Pauline, Teo, that\'s enough children, you have to be patient, go back to your place. Intervene Sister Caroline.\n
Simon found out who Teo was. A little boy of just six, red hair, scarlet complexion and a mischievous look.\n
- Well, here you are, you really exist. He thought.Simon watched the little troop moving away towards the end of the main hallway. A reception room was hidden behind a heavy wooden door painted blue. On the windows a large amount of gold paper stars and clouds of cotton hydrophilic plunged the visitor into a wadded atmosphere. Carried away by curiosity, Simon slipped through a side door. The sight he watched dropped his armor. In the middle of the room stood a fir tree decorated with garlands and multicolored balls, a life-size crib illuminated the room in all its majesty. But above all dozens of little pairs of eyes sparkled in front of so many symbols of peace and love.\n
Simon had just understood why Christmas is magic! The inconsolable grumpy old man wiped tears from his cheeks, then returned to the reception desk.\n
- But where is this Santa Claus costume? Finally ! Hurry, the children are waiting for me.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire2">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Alex Trepov</item>
            <item name="genre">Romance</item>
            <item name="titre">Three times nothing</item>
            <item name="resume">A crazy story in romance!</item>
            <item name="histoire">
He wrote Pute on the wall. With a black paint job as an exclamation point. It\'s puffing gently. The rain offers fluffy patterns to tired lamp posts. They flash without choosing, strip of strobes at a discount. Adam recovers the divinely dirty water in the palm of his hands. He hates those hands. He would like to tear them away. Swing them in the trash like this acrylic bomb. They still remember the softness of her skin, trembling at the thought of not touching it anymore. They bleed at the entournures. If the flesh has no soul, he loses his in abundance. The pain remains liberating. Without hands he would still see his smile, so perhaps it would be better to get out of his eyes. Both of a sudden. Implode her memories, at the source.\n
\n
"When men can not change things, they change the words. "\n
\n
He wrote Love on the wall. With a pink paint job as a question mark. It sparkles slowly. The drizzle caresses the dream of a dim light. The orange spectrum warms the humid atmosphere without ever rushing it. Adam is drinking between heaven and earth, his hands catching every drop of life. He adores his hands. He would like to cuddle them. Keep them open and reassuring like the flowers in the spring. They still remember the softness of her skin, trembling at the thought of tasting it again. They shine with excitement. If the flesh has no soul, he celebrates his in unison. Happiness remains excessive. With his hands still caressing his smile, so maybe he\'d better close his eyes. Both of a sudden. Get drunk with memories, at the source.\n
\n
"We remember nothing, and since we forget everything, nothing is better than anything. "\n
\n
He did not write anything on the wall. A simple squirt of red paint as points of suspension. It fucks the camp gently. The drizzle rattles without echo; the light shines on only what we already know. Adam soaks his dreams, his hands plunged into pockets as empty as he is. He finds them useless. He would like to change it. Have enough to catch the dreams that escape him. They still remember the softness of her skin, bruised at not lingering longer. They sometimes shy away. If the flesh has no soul, he knocks his with his fingers. The abandonment remains. His hands are drawing a cross on his smile, so maybe he\'d better open his eyes. Both of a sudden. Face his memories, at the source.\n
\n
"In all things, the end is essential. "</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire3">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Writeria</item>
            <item name="genre">Humor</item>
            <item name="titre">On the other side</item>
            <item name="resume">A short and funny story!</item>
            <item name="histoire">
"I\'ll still be dead soon ... Anyway. The desperation of life transgressed through each of my words. The nurse at my bedside, who had not made any gestures so far, frowned disapprovingly.\n
\n
He handed me a glass of water while stating his medical knowledge:\n
- You are not going to die Mr. Eriksen, you still have beautiful moments to live!\n
- To hell. Eighty-nine years ago that I pierce the ozone layer, I will not blow this nine-fold decade.\n
- But your family ...\n
- Have you seen someone approaching less than ten meters since I was here? I\'m too old to have parents out of the graveyard, my sister is a bitch it\'s good not to meet and never a peronelle gave me the rope around his neck, finally on the finger ...\n
\n
Miming the last hour of a hanged man, I laughed when the young boy rolled his eyes, but soon a coughing fit made me flip a piece of the glass in my hand and reminded me that there was no time to these kids. More than a few minutes, I felt it ... The end, soon. The young Tom, of his original name, came up to me and put his hand on my forehead. His grimace was as subtle as a blow in the waltzes. He wanted to keep me alive, more than I should have. But he did not suspect the gift that this long-awaited sleep would make me.\n
\n
- Approaching p\'tit, closer ... Here ... I can now count the minutes I have left on both hands, so I\'ll reveal something that will change your life. You ... Before that, are you a believer?\n
- Believer? Tom wondered, having never seen the old man turn to any religion.\n
- Yes, Mass, Rabbis, Shiva and all that bullshit.\n
- Well, I was baptized, but I never really thought that ...\n
- Good. Everyone can believe what he wants, but it will greatly facilitate our task. Well, when you were a kid, you probably heard about Hell and Paradise ...\n
- Yes.\n
- Bullshit. When you die, you die. Do not try to believe that a man from the top of his cloud will find your nice mouth and make you climb to heaven. The only way to get there is to kiss ...\n
- Okay ! OK I understand. Death is dead. Nothing after.\n
- Did I say that ?\n
- But ...\n
- Leave it alone. It was a bad idea ...\n
Tired, I closed the debate even before he could balk. My eyes followed my mouth, and I fell asleep without even resting the still balancing glass on my lap. When I opened my eyes, I was alone in the room and the sun seemed to be gone to bed too. I stayed a few moments rocked by the sound of the machines around me and by the drip of a pocket of transparent liquid connected to my vein. All this mess when I could have been quietly at home, in my chair and with a small beer.\n
\n
The empty bed to my left indicated that my former roommate had made the leap since this morning. And my hour was late and late. I had believed in the end earlier, but it seemed like I was in a hurry. I thought back to that Gisele next door, so scared to leave. In truth, people are afraid of being forgotten, that\'s all. How could I have been afraid of being forgotten when no one knew me? Except Gisele. For six days. But she was dead, so it did not really matter. Maybe that\'s why we put all the old people in the same rooms: story they share their loneliness before putting a definitive end.\n
\n
Mu by a force that I thought had long since disappeared, I opened the drawer of the bedside table and took out a blank sheet and a rather recalcitrant pen. The sheet not so blank, contained figures and diagrams crooked on the back, perhaps an important paper for my care ... Anyway I was going to die, so who would not care! In a wobbly handwriting because of lack of support, I scribbled on paper, my thoughts without any filter.\n

"To die is ... it\'s frankly the best thing that can happen to you. Do not be afraid to live your life, but you will get tired and that, believe my experience is the most boring. Have a body that does not follow your mind ... As well have a fucking race car and have to pedal to advance. Do not get caught. Nobody will tell you, because no one has ever come back to tell you, well, that\'s what we believe. Open your kid spirit!\n
Death is just a bridge. Yes, a bridge, which starts with your life and brings you to a second life (if that word can apply in the other world), which looks much better! I will check this soon, by myself. Do not ask yourself how I know it, it\'s not important (and you would not believe me). Just say that being afraid of death is stupid and useless, because in the end, you leave a rotten world for a much better one.\n
The morons who invented this idea of ​​a "better world" for their so-called paradise could not have been better off. Like what religion can say something other than bullshit ... Without doing it on purpose.\n
I\'m not going to go on for a hundred years, God, I do not want to stay that long ... Just, I\'m not saying goodbye, but see you later. We\'ll see each other once you\'re dead (knowing the truth, you can even hope it happens as soon as possible).\n
Emile Eriksen »\n
\n
Once the letter was completed, I folded the sheet and two and wrote the name "TOM" on one side. A stream of air froze the room and, turning towards the window, I noticed that it was closed. A smile crossed my face. I took the piece of paper between my hands and put it on my belly, the body lying straight and straight, then I took a deep breath and exhaled.\n
For the last time.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire4">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Michel Dréan</item>
            <item name="genre">Drama</item>
            <item name="titre">The city was jubilant</item>
            <item name="resume">A dramatic story, dare you read it?</item>
            <item name="histoire">
The city was jubilant. The crowds all around, exulting. In the square an orchestra played the tunes of java and musette. The exuberance of a false happiness too long contained. How could I forget while I was there, in the midst of those laughter, those radiant faces, those people who kissed? The sun was high in the sky and made me blink.\n
But the war is only losers. All who laughed, danced, saluted the liberators all had deep scars, ghosts who already haunted their paths and would continue to touch the days to come, relatives left not to return. The war left behind only a long carmine furrow, sobs stifled in the sweetness of a summer evening, infinite regrets of not being able to find the words when it was still time while at this moment the Cold ashes would never warm up bruised hearts. I was there and you too. I was there and I did not forget.\n
\n
As I am here today. Facing you waking up slowly. I have not forgotten. Forgetting is something that is forbidden to me. Everything would be so much simpler otherwise. Erase the days that clutter us. To wipe out the indecent hours, the glue of the past that sticks to the soul and freezes our monstrous memories. But all this is impossible. I know it.
You open your eyes.\n
\n
- Damn, what am I doing here?\n
\n
Your voice is pasty. You look defeated. Life is a defeat. You were more boastful last night when you thought I was easy prey. This meeting that you thought was guided by chance. These glasses tied on the terrace of this bistro. The last one I offered you at home where you slumped like a mass. I must say that I had put the dose.\n
\n
- But answer brothel!\n
- So you do not remember anything?\n
- Are you crazy or what? Come loose.\n
\n
I caress the long pair of tapered scissors with my hand. I like the idea that you are entirely at my mercy. I think I\'m smiling. Oh, not a sign of joy, a smirk, a bad grimace. Sorry, that\'s all I have in reserve. For you, that will be enough.\n
\n
- I\'ll cut your balls.\n
\n
Suddenly, you do not know what to think. I see the fear in the bottom of your pupils. It is incrusted, sweet. Small bursts of pure fear that shine like diamonds. Am I going to act? Right now or will I make you wait a bit?\n
\n
- Shit but what did I do to you?\n
\n
What did you do to me ! The city was jubilant. You were on the safe side, resistant to the last hour, stashed all the time in your mother\'s skirts. Black market and probably worse. Good people, servile and opportunistic. Passed into the victors\' camp when the wind had turned. The crowd all around screaming. The orchestra. How could I forget?\n
I approach you, the scissors well in evidence. I grab your hair and pull your head back. A first wick falls, then another and another again.\n
- Help, help!\n
- You can shout as much as you want, nobody will hear you here, it\'s too isolated.\n
\n
I recognized you last week. How to forget your face? Obviously it was not reciprocal. It must be said that I changed since then and that day I did not look like much. Me and the other girls. Standing on this truck platform. The city was jubilant. The crowd was screaming. Insults, spitting.\n
\n
No, but I dream, you pissed in your pants, you the hero of liberation. Courage, you had to shear us before the populace revenge. You had put heart to the work. Blouse torn off, my chest to the air, they had for their money. And the blondness of my hair harvested. Every handle that fell was raising its share of cheers. My shame drunk, sip after sip. And then when you let them let off steam a little on my humiliated body, you forgot?\n
\n
I do not, I remember again and again the fruit of this forbidden love lost in a flood of black blood. I remember Hans, shot by yours at home, while he aspired to one thing: to surrender, to erase forever this murderous madness that before the world ignited. He was not a Nazi. No, he was just on the wrong side. Love does not wear a uniform, it has no flag, no country, no border. But how could you understand that, you the coward, judge and executioner.\n
\n
No city in jubilation. No orchestra, no java or musette, no cheers, no foamy crowd when your last handful of hair falls. Just you and me. I look at you one last time before cutting your links. You can go with your shaven head, your ugliness. Get out of here before I change my mind. Get out of the way with your dirty pants, with your facts of glory and your lies.\n
\n
I stay with my memories.\n
With Hans and this child who could have been born.\n
With this future extinct.\n
I do not even feel better.\n
</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire5">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Auriane Calvés</item>
            <item name="genre">Instant of life</item>
            <item name="titre">It was enough of a night</item>
            <item name="resume">A moment of life, a story!</item>
            <item name="histoire">
I had put down my pen and inkwell. I had abandoned the words and clichés. Since his departure, I could not find the desire to align two sentences on my keyboard.\n
\n
Stretched out in an old leather sofa, I was immersed in a new novel telling the story of two friends who had packed up to reach Scotland and its abandoned lighthouses. I pulled on my cigarette and then exhaled a puff of smoke that he had taught me to dance. On the low table, a piece of Armenian paper was consumed and embalmed the room with a delicate amber perfume. The small bedside lamp placed by my side, comforted me with its subdued atmosphere.\n
\n
It was late at night when the first flakes began to fall in the empty streets of Manhattan. Through the veranda, I now observed the breeze slowly marry these snow-covered pearls that we covet in the winter. That evening, I felt his presence watching over me like the clouds that protect the little men from the baking sun. That night, I felt it was time to give up the void that resonated in me since leaving for the azure seas.\n
\n
I waited a few hours before awakening Mael, who, immersed in his imaginary world, took a while to emerge fully. I took pleasure in plunging my face into the bottom of her bubbling neck, drowning my hands in her wavy hair that slipped through my fingers like silk. I tenderly kissed his sleepy face as he whispered in the hollow of my ear, "Where are we going mom?" I plunged into the apple of his eyes, which reminded me so much of the one I had loved for years, and replied: "We are going on a manic adventure. "\n
\n
We left Manhattan in the middle of the night to reach the airport. Sitting in the back of the yellow taxi, Mael had put his head against the misted window. The lights of the street lamps and billboards captivated him. When we arrived at JFK, I had no idea where to go. Fortunately I had enough savings for the adventure. I then crouched down to grab my son\'s hands. They were so small and only needed to grow around the world. I plunged my eyes into his own before questioning him: "The adventure is where? And it is with a great simplicity, but without surprise, that he replied to me "Where is dad! "\n
\n
He was still too young to understand that the world was no longer reserving dad\'s adventures. But he was not too young to fly there where Dad would have liked to travel ... This was the legacy he had left us: the desire to wander. So we flew to Bolivia. Then came trips and roadtrips, discoveries and daydreams, cravings and follies. And for the first time since leaving, I relived.\n
\n
It was finally enough of a night inhabited by snowy pearls to give me the desire to align two sentences on my keyboard ...</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire6">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Kaimeng</item>
            <item name="genre">Suspense, Humor</item>
            <item name="titre">The interviews of a jaded killer</item>
            <item name="resume">A killer like no other.</item>
            <item name="histoire">
I remember a black sofa and milky white walls.\n
I was lying down. Turning my head to the right, I could see through the window the raindrops tickling the windows. There was a whirlwind and the rippling of the water echoed in my ears.\n
The apartment was spacious and nice. The living room was warm and lined with sumptuous tapestries. A huge television was hanging on the wall in front of me. A half-open door revealed a modern and very well maintained kitchen. Everything had been arranged with taste by the owner of the place, my interlocutor, who was seated on a brown Chesterfield armchair, which was at my side. He was observing me with his brown eyes as I talked to him, my feelings and doubts, I had problems so I needed to talk to a psychologist, while lying on a couch.\n
\n
- Have I always wanted to do this work? I do not think so. You see, after high school, I did not see myself entering the world of work like everyone else. I wanted to do something extraordinary, unique. I arrived in this area by chance and now it\'s been years since I killed to live. But I\'m getting sick of it.\n
\n
The man muttered something that I interpreted as a question about what I really wanted.\n
\n
- Difficult answer. I need challenge, adventure. You know it\'s not easy for me, it\'s the first time I talk about myself that way.\n
\n
He then mumbled some intelligible words, which I understood as questions about my childhood. I\'ll give you the details of my answer because I do not think that would really captivate you.
All I can tell you is that studying you would surely have bored all the profilers that we see in the American series on TV. Because, I want to tell you now, I was not raped in my childhood, my father did not put on dresses to disguise me, and I did not start killing animals at the age of eight years. I must say that I had a rather quiet childhood and a normal adolescence. Drugs, girls, alcohol, cigarettes, I got everything I wanted on time and I was very happy with my life at the time.
That\'s exactly what I said to my interlocutor. I saw the surprise in his eyes. It is true that we would wait for another answer from a guy who declares aloud that he is a killer. I was probably the first person he had met in his life. I was used to this kind of reaction.\n
\n
- I promise you, I do not do this job for pleasure. In any case, not for a while. I have, for the moment, no other plan for the future so I continue. I must tell you, before you are really disappointed, that the job of a hitman has nothing to do with what you see in the movies. It\'s not so exciting. The big part of my job is the murder of a husband or wife sponsored by their spouse.\n
\n
I heard my interlocutor moan, which made me realize my indelicacy.\n
\n
- Yes, I\'m sorry ... That\'s the case today. When she came to see me, she told me that you were a psychologist so I thought that talking to you a little would do me good. I\'m really bad ... I do not know where I\'m going with my life.\n
He tried to speak again, it was then that I realized that I had spent too much time in this apartment, with this man I did not understand any of the words. It must be said that the gag that I had introduced between the teeth did not facilitate his speech, I must admit. I needed to be listened to, heard but I did not care what he could tell me. And I did not want him to ram the whole neighborhood home. I do a job that goes very well with this kind of advertising.
I raised my weapon, a Beretta 92 that I had bought at the beginning of my career and from which I never parted. The scratch on the handle was the only trace that could be seen, otherwise it was in perfect condition. I took care of it like the apple of my eyes. Have you ever seen someone not paying attention to his work tool? It is unthinkable!
Seeing the weapon, the man began to gesticulate, and to shout under his rag. Terror could be read in his eyes. He stared at the weapon trying to figure out what he had done to deserve what was going to happen to him. That\'s when I let go:\n
\n
- You should have married another woman.\n
\n
Then I pressed the trigger.\n
His head was first recoiled by the shock before tilting forward.\n
His muffled cries fell silent.\n
I did some cleaning and left the apartment. Death was again spent doing its job.\n
I went out, the rain continued to fall. I was soaked.\n
Without hope, my life was hopeless, without hope. I sighed, already thinking about my next contract. Too bad there is no pension fund for killers.\n
As I told him, the big part of my job was the murder of a husband or wife sponsored by their spouse.\n
If I told you how many contracts I had, I think you would not want to get married.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire7">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Christophe</item>
            <item name="genre">Horror</item>
            <item name="titre">Stuffed cabbage</item>
            <item name="resume">Dare to read despite the chills?</item>
            <item name="histoire">
Corpses on glossy paper. Men are necrophiles! Satin ears, fur gloves, silk stockings, you look like a rabbit whose fur has been torn off. The males wilt themselves while contemplating you, but their fingers slide on the pages triturated a hundred times. To appease their hunger, they fall back on the dishes prepared by their women, real women with soft and tepid skin, they no longer look. I buy whole rabbits. It\'s cheaper and the meat keeps its game taste. Tapered knife. I plunge the blade down the belly and back up to the sternum. The gash vomits the entrails of the beast. I reserve them in a tupperware. The organs are delightfully pranks. Every night, I prepare a dish that my man likes. I know his taste on the tips of his fingers, which he sucks to the last drop of sauce. It is a predator that likes fresh meat. In ten years, I learned how to cut it and cook it to best express its flavor. I like working it, discovering its hidden paths, its resistance, its texture. I respect her and my blade always follows the path she tells me.\n
After a sleepless night, like every morning, I eat breakfast alone. My man did not come home. Her sex is always stronger than her belly and the other, the young, satiates him still. But that will not last. One evening, it will ring. He will not have the courage to use his keys. Men are cowards. They are conquerors until the first night, then they arrange their sword and offer you their crown. The knight becomes an accountant of the day, weighing what you bring him and what you cost him. Woe to the one who leans too much on this side of the scale!\n
I\'ll open the door without a word. He will wait for a moment, eyes downcast, begging for a pardon that will restore his appetite. Before my silence, he will enter the apartment. In the dining room, he will discover, on a valet, a white shirt and an impeccably ironed suit. He will involuntarily cast a glance at his own crumpled sleeve, but will repress it immediately. Then, he will stop as a comedian lack of inspiration.
Actor !\n
I sat down at the table. A pot will let escape perfumed vapors of rabbit with mustard. Still without a word, I will fill his plate.
A ladle. Two ladles.\n
We will eat. Only the muffled sound of our cutlery will disturb the silence of our reunion. He will control his actions in order to make the least possible noise, funambulist at the limit of existence. In his eyes, I will see fear, shame, gluttony and guilt. Cruel farandole of the feelings of the man fed by the woman he betrayed!\n
Then, I\'ll go and wash. He will wait for me in the bed, dressed in the pajamas he has found folded on a chair. He will not dare to wash his teeth. This activity is only practiced in couple or with friends and it will not know in which category I put it. Unless he\'s afraid to see a used toothbrush taunt him with tooth glass.\n
I will lie down beside him and we will simultaneously extinguish our bedside lamps. Like before.\n
There, for the first time, he will outline a male gesture of attempt at reconciliation.\n
And there, for the first time, I will speak:\n
- No !\n
He will exhale that sigh I know so well, will turn on his right side and fall asleep.\n
I will then grab the knife under the mattress and plant it in its offered liver. Death will be quick and painless, leaving meat firmness and tenderness. That\'s how I like men. I will reserve the organs in a tupperware for a joke.\n
A week later, the meat has matured enough to be prepared in Burgundy. I\'ll invite Jacques, my husband\'s best friend, to dinner. Jacques supported me when he left me, but I quickly realized that this support was interested. When Jacques declared himself, when he crossed the border without return where we would like to desire the wife of his best friend, I promised to give him the day when I would be convinced that my couple had no chance to rebuild.\n
I will keep my promise.\n
In the evening, he will ring at my house. The smell of the Burgundian will hardly compete with that of the huge bouquet he will offer me. In conquering, Jacques will enter the apartment. In the dining room, he will breathe, satisfied, the smell of the hot dish on the table. I will give myself to him without waiting. In men, sex passes before the stomach. Then we will sit down and watch him shred the remains of my past.\n
That one, I\'m going to be suspicious of it. A man who betrays a friend will have no qualms about betraying a woman. But to see his powerful jaws, his lips covered with sauce and his eyes lost with pleasure, I know that it will be enough for me to satisfy his belly so that it remains for me.\n
Tomorrow, I\'ll make stuffed cabbage!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="histoire8">
            <item name="annee">2018</item>
            <item name="auteur">Clément Paquis</item>
            <item name="genre">Horror</item>
            <item name="titre">The power of the mad</item>
            <item name="resume">Dare to read despite the chills?</item>
            <item name="histoire">
It was a Tuesday morning, moments before the council of ministers, that Charles Bouvier decided to massacre all his family with the help of a circular saw. In about twenty minutes, Bouvier reduced to lint his wife, his three children as well as the dog. The information caused a scandal, so that the Minister of Agriculture was dispatched in a hurry to speak and respond to the screams that came to him from social networks.\n
"The government is deeply shocked by this barbaric act, and we are determined to respond to it in the strongest possible way, including the immediate, total and definitive ban on circular saws inside the building. Hexagon. "\n
On social networks, we sighed with relief, and then we track down the singer, the actor, the politician or TV presenter humor definitely too black or too daring to be consistent with these progressive values who are ours.\n
\n
Two months later, shortly before the President of the Republic paid tribute to the martyrs of the Great War, it was learned that Tarik Benboulian, thirty-four, had decided to make soup with the genitals of his wife, all seasoned with a handful of rosemary, salt and olive oil.\n
" Always the same ! Screamed the right of the social networks, demanding that the death penalty, the torture, be reinstated, and that the prisons be reopened to make work for life and in pain those manure assassins that soiled everything hope to one day apply the living-together to our beautiful country.\n
The secretary of state for gastronomy immediately took the floor, assuring that the government was not going to stop there, and was going to enact imminently, a law devolved to regulate the sale of olive oil, rosemary, and that a particular surveillance would be applied in order to keep an eye on the consumers of Provence herbs.\n
\n
When three months later, Jacques Grosbouillon murdered his neighbor and his entire family, tearing their brains out of their heads to make a terrine campaign, social networks thundered in unison that it was a scandal, and that the power had a real interest to act before the return of the dark years was felt.\n
\n
The President of the Republic therefore spoke in person, and announced that no measure would be taken by the power. In the face of cries of protest from the Internet, he hastened to point out that it was already forbidden for a long time to be in possession of a brain on the territory of the Republic, and that this law had been rigorously applied. by the good people of France.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
